# Ahmed Siddique

03495486080



www.linkedin.com/in/ahmed-siddique- in

2a1918247/

I Studying a Computer Science Degree in Air University in 2020. As an enthusiast of learning new things I started my coding journey by making projects. I have a strong grip in logic building and analytical thinking. My current CGPA is 3.31 and in third semester I also acquired the merit base scholarship in air university. In my 3 years coding journey these are one of my projects:

- Flight Reservation System with OOP concepts
- Library management system with Django.
- Make Ludo with C++ and multithreading.
- Clone GitHub pages, Todo list, calculator with css html JavaScript
- ❖ Todo list, cart system in react, tic tac toe game with react.
- Python space hunter game with Pyame.

## **Experience**

SEPTEMBER 2022 - OCTOBER 2022

#### Let's GROW MORE/ Flutter Developer

I Completed my 1-month Internship in Mobile Application Developer in LETS GROW More. I have a wonderful experience to be work as a flutter developer in the group.

JUNE 2022 - AUGUST 2022

#### PSEB IT Industry Academia Bridge Program 2022

I enjoy a wonderful experience of Academia bridge program in Mobile App Development Flutter.

JANUARY 2023 - FEBRUARY 2022

#### **AUCIS Web Development Boot camp 2023**

After a semester I avail my free time to enhance my skill by taking AUCIS web development boot camp.

### Skills

CSS HTML JavaScript
Django as backend
Flutter
Dart
Machine Learning
React

## **Education**

SEPTEMBER 2020 - PRESENT

Bachelor in Computer Science / Air University, Islamabad,

## **Activities**

Book Reading
Cricket